<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Roamify</string>
    <string name="hotels">HOTELS</string>
    <string name="water_activity">WATER ACTIVITIES</string>
    <string name="air_activity">AIR ACTIVITIES</string>
    <string name="land_activity">LAND ACTIVITIES</string>
    <string name="contact_us">CONTACT</string>
    <string name="about_us">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="destination">DESTINATIONS</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">ActivityDetails</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyB6UsGqed0995VNE4uvDieRKDrjRMxL6pk</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page_with_menu">HomePageWithMenu</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="no_network_title">No Internet</string>
    <string name="no_network_msg">Error connecting with server. Network may be down. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="aboutus">Remember the time when you saw a cloud covered mountain with a small valley of beautiful huts and a pool by the side. The smell of daisies and the bloom of tulips, the chirp of birds and the croak of crickets, the vast stretch of green grass and snow covered peaks. Remember the last time you saw a mountain. Clam and quiet, standing in it’s own thoughts with head held high.\n\n“The pursuit of science has often been compared to the scaling of mountains, high and not so high. But who amongst us can hope, even in imagination, to scale the Everest and reach its summit when the sky is blue and the air is still, and in the stillness of the air survey the entire Himalayan range in the dazzling white of the snow stretching to infinity? None of us can hope for a comparable vision of nature and of the universe around us. But there is nothing mean or lowly in standing in the valley below and awaiting the sun to rise over Kanchenjunga. ”</string>
</resources>
